{
    "id": "7debcf8d2b724828be4685080599155a",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the book ……………………",
            "description": "When the object of the preposition is the relative pronoun that, the preposition is always placed at the end.",
            "answers": [
                "that you were looking for",
                "for that you were looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………… the top of his class.",
            "description": "We use at to speak of things at rest.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The snake crawled ………………… its hole.",
            "description": "We use into to speak of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where I live in",
                "in that I live",
                "I live in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat sprang …………………. the table.",
            "description": "We use upon to speak of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………… the end of the street.",
            "description": "Until and till are used to talk about time to talk about distance we use to or up to.",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I slept …………………. 9 o’clock.",
            "description": "We use till to talk about time.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "up to",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t eaten anything …………………. yesterday.",
            "description": "Since is used to indicate some point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been ill …………………… many days.",
            "description": "For is used with a period of time.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not seen him …………………. last week.",
            "description": "Since is used to indicate some point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He will join work ……………………. tomorrow.",
            "description": "From is also used with a noun or phrase indicating a point of time, but unlike since it is used with all the tenses.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. his children, his nephews and nieces were present there.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "Besides",
                "Beside"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}